I'm going to demonstrate how to work within the Lab Workspace.
现在我将来讲解 lab 中 workspace 的使用方法
Click on the three blue bars in the left upper corner.
点击左上角的三道小蓝杠
This opens up the Navigation Pane,
打开导航栏
scroll down until you see the Lab Workspace and click on it.
下拉到 lab workspace 处 单击
This opens up your Lab Workspace.
打开 lab workspace
It's composed of three sections.
workspace 包括三个部分
The first section has the files.
第一部分是放文件的地方
The second section is where you open and edit files.
第二部分是打开和编辑文件的地方
The third section allows you to open
第三部分是打开终端窗口的地方
terminal windows so that you can run your Python programs.
你可以在此运行 Python 程序
Let's open a Terminal window by clicking on the plus.
单击加号按钮 打开一个终端窗口
While the Terminal window initializes,
趁终端窗口还在初始化
let's expand the Edit window.
我们先放大编辑窗口
If I click on check images,
如果我点击 check_images
this brings it up in the Edit window and then I can add my name beside
文件就会出现在编辑窗口中 这样我就可以在 programmer 一栏输入自己的名字了
programmer and it automatically saves it.
文件会自动保存
So, now check images has my name in it.
现在 check_images 里就有我的名字了
So when you're editing check images for the lab,
也就是说 在 lab 里编辑 check_images
the changes you make in this program are automatically saved.
lab 会把修改自动保存下来
To run this program Check Images,
要运行程序 check_images
you go to the Terminal window and just type Python space check.
就在终端窗口里输入 “python” 然后空格 然后输入 “check”
And then if you hit tab,
这个时候如果你按 tab 键
you'll get tab completion,
就会激活 tab 自动补全功能
which will complete the file name and you can hit enter and it will run the program.
文件名会自动补全 之后按下 enter 键 程序就会开始运行
While it's running, let's go back and look at the files in our directory here.
趁程序还在运行 我们回来看目录这边的文件
We have the pet images folder.
这里有文件夹 pet_images
If I click on it,
点击该文件夹
I see all the pet images.
就能看到所有的宠物图像
To go back, I click on the arrow up here and it puts me back in that Workspace directory.
要返回 点击这上面的箭头就可以回到 workspace 的目录里了
The only file I should be changing in here is check images.
这里我要修改的文件只有 check_images
If I want to close check images out,
如果想关闭 check_images
I just hit the X and it closes out.
只需点击这个 X 文件就关闭了
If I want to open up something else like dognames.txt,
如果我想打开其它文件 比如 dognames.txt
I click on it and it opens in this Edit window.
那就点击该文件 文件就会在编辑窗口中打开了
Let's say I make a mistake and I accidentally delete or change dognames.txt.
假设我错误操作 无意删除或修改了 dognames.txt
So, if I right click and hit Delete,
比如我右键点击了删除按钮
I will delete it and all of a sudden it's gone.
删除了文件 那文件就会消失
To be able to bring dog names back,
为了还原 dognames
I need to reset my environment,
我需要重设环境
but when I reset,
可环境一旦重设
it's going to set back to the original state,
整个 workspace 都会回到初始状态
which will mean the change that I made in
也就意味着我在
check images by adding my name is going to disappear.
check_images 里做出的修改 添加的名字都会消失
So, to keep from losing check images,
因此 为了保留 check_images 的修改
I need to download it.
我得把文件下载下来
I click on Check Images,
点击 check_images
do right click and Download and it will download to my Downloads folder on my laptop.
用右键点击 单击下载 文件就会下载到电脑的 Download 文件夹里了
We can also see here that our program finished running,
我们可以看到 这里的程序已经运行完毕了
total elapsed runtime is none, that's expected.
总运行时间为 None 这是在意料之中的
This demonstrates how to run your Python program within this Workspace.
这里呈现了 workspace 运行 Python 程序的过程
Our file is downloaded so now we can safely reset the Workspace to its original state.
文件已经下载好了 现在我们可以放心地将 workspace 重置为初始状态了
I hit Menu and then Reset Data to
依次单击菜单和重置数据
reset your data because you're overwriting everything that you've worked on,
将数据重置 因为你要覆盖之前处理过的所有数据
you need to type in Reset data and make sure you have a lower case D,
所以你要输入 “Reset data” 注意 “data” 首字母小写
once it's typed correctly it'll initialize this button,
正确输入后 这个按钮就会激活
you hit it and it resets all the data.
点击按钮 数据就重置了
So, now I would expect that I see dog names is back and if I click on it, there it is.
如我所料 dognames 复原了 点击该文件 里面的内容都在
So, it's reset back to its original state.
一切都重置成初始状态了
If I click on check images,
如果我点击 check_images
I see that I don't see my name typed
就会发现我的名字消失了
in here because it's the original state of the program.
因为这是程序的初始状态
To bring my edited program back,
要还原编辑过的程序
I just click on check images, right click,
只需右键单击 check_images
and do Delete and then I delete it.
删除该文件 删除好后
And now, I click on this plus and hit Upload File.
点击这个加号 然后点击文件上传
And I go to my Downloads directory,
来到 Downloads 目录下
click on check images,
点击 check_images
open, and it uploads that file that I edited back to my Workspace.
打开该文件 修改好的文件就会重新上传到 workspace 里
If I double click on it,
双击该文件
there it is Jennifer S, that's me.
就能看到里面有我的名字 Jennifer S 了
And this is that file that I edited.
这就是我修改过的那个文件
I would recommend that you download
建议你把文件 check_images 下载下来
your check images file before you do the reset so that you save your work.
再去重置 这样才能把修改保留下来
You can also upload other files you want to the Workspace by using
你也可以上传其它文件到 workspace 中
the plus and then upload a file or upload a folder.
只需点击加号 选择要上传文件还是文件夹即可
So, to go back to the lessons,
要回到课程里
I simply click on the three bars on
只需点击左上角的三道小蓝杠
the upper left corner that opens the navigation pane and then I pick my lesson.
打开导航窗格 选择课程
I'm going back to Workspace How-to,
我要回到 “如何使用 workspace” 一课中
click on it and it opens back up.
因此点击该标签 回到课程里
And if I want to expand that,
如果想放大该界面
I click on these three bars again and expands my Workspace How-to,
那就再点击那三道小蓝杠
to be full screen.
“如何使用 workspace” 界面就全屏了